FABIO PETRELLA

Full Stack Developer

() +49 (0) 17614376528 @ fbpetrella@gmail.com

Personal Portfolio Personal Portfolio Personal Portfolio

SUMMARY

Web Developer with ability to learn and collaborate in rapidly changing environments, a 1-year intensive training in Full Stack Web Development (MERN stack) and many hours of self-taught coding. Seeking for a position to apply the results of my previous experiences combined with acquired skills, to challenge myself and deliver creative solutions.

Highly motivated, critical thinker and team-work oriented.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Developer DCI Digital Career Institue gGmbH

2021 - Ongoing Berlin, DE

- $\circ \ \ \text{Accomplishing a one-year-full-time training including technologies from MERN stack}$
- o Completing multiple small and one final practical project to practice programming skills

Food SpecialistL'Aquila, IT

2014 - 2015 L'Aquila, IT

Niko Romito Formazione e Consulenza SRL

- Accomplished a nine-month-full-time training, Reale, Michelin 3 Star Restaurant
- o Completed final exam with a rating of 52/60

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sous-Chef

03/2019 - 12/2019 Berlin, DE

Lab Kitchen, act.3 GmbH

- o Responsible for managing and directing the kitchen staff, shifts and job positions
- o Developed new menu options based on seasonal changes and customer demand
- Ensured that kitchen activities operate in a timely manner

Chef de Partie

03/2018 - 02/2019 Berlin, DE

A Common Ground, Silo Coffee GmbH

- o Gave attention productivity of the kitchen such as speed and food quality
- o Provided support to junior kitchen employees with various tasks including line cooking
- o Recruited and trained new kitchen employees to meet restaurant and kitchen standards



Javascript React Typescript
ES6 SASS CSS3 Bootstrap
HTML5 NodeJs MongoDB
Express JsonWebToken Git

PROJECTS

EV-Connection

Full Stack App built with React, ExpressJS, MongoDb, Leaflet_

https://evconnection.herokuapp.com

SightSpot

Full Stack App built with React, ExpressJS, Bootstrap

https://sightspot.herokuapp.com/

Rock, Paper, Scissors

Game built with Javascript, CSS, Html https://fbgameproject.netlify.app/

CERTIFICATES

Udemy - Typescript Course 2022

Udemy - Javascript Course 2022

LANGUAGES

Italian - Native Speaker

English - Full Professional Proficiency

German - Prof. Working Proficiency

Spanish - Elementary Proficiency

LINKS









Fabio Petrella, geboren am 07.12.1986

nimmt seit 06.10.2021 bis voraussichtlich 09.12.2022 an unserem Institut an folgender Maßnahme teil:

Weiterbildung zum/zur Web- und Softwareentwickler/-in

Im Rahmen der Maßnahme hat der Teilnehmer bereits folgende berufspraktische und theoretische Schulungen zum Zwecke der Weiterbildung absolviert:

Inhalte:

Basic Digital Literacy - 64 UE
UI Basics - 288 UE
Programming Basics - 288 UE
Single Page Application - 288 UE
Backend - 288 UE
Finales Abschlussprojekt - 224 UE
Berufsbezogener Deutsch-/Englischunterricht - 200 UE
Soft Skills - 64 UE

Berufsbezogener Englischunterricht - Niveau Lower Intermediate 3 Final Project wurde als Gruppenarbeit absolviert: EV Connection

> DI Digital Career Institute

Unterschrift & Stempel DCI gGmbH

Berlin, 11.10.2022





CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION

Typescript: The Complete Developer's Guide

Instructors Stephen Grider

Fabio Petrella

Date Nov. 2, 2022 Length 24.5 total hours



Certificate no: UC-21b96142-54c5-4c57-b036-bddc4c275c00

Certificate url: ude.my/UC-21b96142-54c5-4c57-b036-bddc4c275c00

Reference Number: 0004

CERTIFICATE OF COMPLETION

The Complete JavaScript Course 2022: From Zero to Expert!

Instructors Jonas Schmedtmann

Fabio Petrella

Date July 1, 2022 Length 69 total hours